<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">GMTMoney</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">GMT MONEY TRANSFER EXCHANGE , 2,2 STATION ST HARRIS PARK,NSW 2150 (GMT MONEY) is a registered business BN 98561094 with parent company Spicy touch Australia pty ltd  ABN 73 140 926 307.\n\nSender refers to a person sending funds to Receiver via GMT MONEY or its nominated agent and Receiver refers to a person receiving funds via GMT MONEY or its nominated agent. GMT MONEY provides a money transfer service whereby GMT MONEY facilitates the transmission of your funds to a person overseas and/or Funds from a person overseas to you. These terms and conditions apply to and govern all money transfers and associated services between you and GMT MONEY. Money transfers can be sent or received from the office of GMT MONEY within the working hours. At present GMT MONEY working hours are 10am to 5pm Monday to Friday and are subject to change. To send a money transfer you must fill the GMT MONEY application form with all the details required and provide a valid photo identification document acceptable to GMT MONEY. You warrant that all information you supply to GMT MONEY is and shall remain accurate and complete. GMT MONEY will use the information provided in this form in order to make available to you money transfer services. GMT MONEY may store your personal information in its data base for the purpose of the administration of its ongoing relationship with you. You have the right to request a copy of certain personal information that GMT MONEY holds about you. GMT MONEY will not share your information with any third parties except as required by law. It is your responsibility to provide GMT MONEY with correct details when using GMT MONEY money transfer services. Further you warrant to GMT MONEY that any money transfer received or sent is for lawful purposes and the information provided to GMT MONEY is correct. GMT MONEY is not under any obligation to accept your application and may decline the same at GMT MONEY discretion. To send a money transfer, you are required to first make payment in cash at the office of GMT MONEY, or deposit cash or cheque in GMT MONEY nominated bank account or transfer funds to GMT MONEY nominated account through internet. Under any mode of payment, your application will only be processed after making the payment by you and against clear available funds in cash or in GMT MONEY account. Maximum permissible amount per transaction for payment to the receiver in cash or deposit in his account at the destination country will apply. Ask GMT MONEY staff for the limits applicable to your transfer. GMT MONEY is required by law to report all send and receive money transfer transactions to regulatory authority. A separate reporting is made to regulatory authority if the amount received or paid A$10,000 or above in cash.\n\nFor money transfer to some countries or in the period of promotion announced by GMT MONEY from time to time, GMT MONEY do not recover any fees or charges from its clients. However, in case of larger amounts, where per transaction limit is applied, the first transaction will be free of cost, whereas subsequent transactions will bear normal fees and charges.\n\nGMT MONEY display exchange rates of various currencies on its web site, which are for indication only and subject to change at any time. Before sending money you must ask and agree the exchange rate given by GMT MONEY and make payment in equivalent local currency plus GMT MONEY fees and charges by cash, cheque or internet transfer. Also make sure the currency and total amount available for payment to the receiver in receive country.\n\nUnless you book or agree an exchange rate with GMT before making the payment, the money transfer will be processed by GMT MONEY at the then prevailing rate after deduction of its fees and charges if any. \n\nIn addition to the service fees and charges applicable in your money transfer, there will be difference in exchange rate set by GMT MONEY for you and received by GMT MONEY from its correspondents. Any exchange rate benefit between the exchange rate given to you and received by GMT MONEY will be kept by GMT MONEY. \n\nGMT MONEY accepts no further responsibility after funds have been paid over the counter, or by cheque handed over personally to the receiver or dispatched at his address or deposited in his nominated account.\n\nPayment of a money transfer may in some circumstances be subject to local taxes and/or service or administrative charges for which the sender and/or receiver may be liable. \n\nThere may be taxation or Goods or Services (GST) implications for you in sending or receiving a money transfer. GMT MONEY advises you to obtain an independent advice from your tax agent or accountant about any such liability or benefit. \n\nGMT MONEY will refund the principal amount of a money transfer upon a written request of the sender if payment to the recipient is not made within 45 days. \n\nAfter processing the transaction, if you, for any genuine reason need to cancel the transaction and ask for the refund, your request will only be processed upon your written cancellation request. GMT MONEY will contact its overseas correspondent and request to cancel the transaction and refund the amount. GMT MONEY will only make the refund to you on receipt of clear funds from its overseas correspondent less GMT MONEY’s cancellation charges and any deduction if made by overseas correspondent. Any exchange difference due to exchange rate fluctuation between the rates fixed for the transaction and the rate prevailing on the date of cancellation of transaction will also be deducted from the refund amount. \n\nGMT MONEY does not guarantee the delivery of the money transfer. You are cautioned against sending money to any person you do not know. In no event shall GMT MONEY or any of its agents or staff members be liable for damages for the delay, non payment or underpayment of this money transfer. In no event GMT MONEY or its agent or staff be liable for any indirect, special, incidental or consequential damages. \n\nGMT MONEY is not liable to carry out GMT Moneys obligations referred to in these terms and conditions if it is not reasonably practicable for GMT MONEY to do so for reasons or events outside GMT Moneys control including but not limited to earthquake, or other act of God, war, loss of telecommunications or essential services, terrorist attack etc. \n\nGMT MONEY reserves the right to change these terms and conditions without notice to you at any time.\n\Other disclosures\n\nPersonal information may be disclosed to:\n\n• brokers and agents who refer your business to GMT MONEY\n\n• any person acting on your behalf, including your financial adviser, solicitor or accountant, executor,\n\nadministrator, trustee, guardian or attorney\n\n• organizations to whom GMT MONEY outsources certain functions.\n\nIn all circumstances where GMT MONEY’s contractors, agents and outsourced service providers become aware of personal information, confidentiality arrangements apply. Personal information may only be used by our agents, contractors and outsourced service providers for GMT MONEY’s purposes.\n\nGMT MONEY may also disclose personal information to other financial institutions and organizations at their request if you seek credit from them.\n\nGMT MONEY may be allowed or obliged to disclose information by law, eg, under Court Orders or Statutory Notices pursuant to taxation or social security laws\n\nAccess to your Personal Information - You may obtain access to most personal information we hold about you by contacting our Compliance Officer. Sometimes there may be a reason why access will not be possible. If that is the case, you will be told why.\n\nWe collect your personal information in order to provide our products and services, satisfy our regulatory obligations under the AML/CTF legislation referred to in paragraph 10 and assess your credit worthiness.\n\nWe may provide your personal information to our intermediary bankers and to any government regulatory bodies that normally require it or may request it. We may also provide your information to any partners, agents or intermediaries who are a necessary part of the provision of our products and services.\n\nYou acknowledge and agree that we use international intermediaries to process Transactions on your behalf and that your personal information may be sent to those overseas intermediaries in order to complete the Transaction.\n\nConsent to Credit Reference Reports– You acknowledge and agree that we may access any electronic databases necessary to assist us to identify you and to assess your credit worthiness. In particular, you agree that we may obtain, use and retain information about you that we have obtained from any business that provides information about the credit worthiness of individuals, including a consumer credit report from a credit reporting agency. In doing so, we may give information about you to a credit reporting agency for the purpose of obtaining a consumer credit report about you and allowing the credit reporting agency to create or maintain a credit information file containing information about you. The information will be limited to your identity particulars, including your name, sex, address (and the previous two addresses), date of birth, name of employer, and drivers license number, as well as the fact that you have made an application for credit to us.\n\nUse of Your Information - You agree that we may use any information we collect about you for the purposes of complying with our obligations under any AML/CTF Regulations and for any other purpose directly related to the provision of our services.\n\nInformation Correct and Up to Date - You must ensure that all information you give to us is accurate and up-to-date at all times. You must tell us if any of your personal details change as soon as practicable.\n\nProtection of Information- We collect and store all information electronically and take all reasonable steps to protect information from unauthorized access, but we cannot accept liability for unauthorized access or use of your personal information.\n\nAny information collected by us, including telephone recordings or transcripts, may be kept or destroyed in accordance with our information retention policy.\n\nRecording Phone Conversations - You consent to the electronic recording of all telephone conversations that take place between us without an automatic warning tone or warning message being given and you agree that we may use the recordings as evidence in any dispute or anticipated dispute between us.\n\nAnti-Money Laundering and Counter-Terrorism Financing (AML/CTF)\n\nAML/CTF Compliance - You undertake that you will not knowingly do anything to put us in breach of the Anti-Money Laundering and Counter-Terrorism Financing Act 2006, rules and other subordinate instruments (AML/CTF Laws). You undertake to notify us if you become aware of anything that would put us in breach of AML/CTF Laws.\n\nProvision of Information - If requested, you undertake to provide additional information and assistance and comply with all reasonable requests to facilitate our compliance with AML/CTF Laws in Australia or an equivalent overseas jurisdiction.\n\nNo Grounds for Suspicion - You undertake that you are not aware and have no reason to suspect that:\n\n(i)         the money you are transferring is derived from or related to money laundering, terrorism financing or similar activities (Illegal Activities) and\n\n(ii)        the money you are transferring will be used to finance, or in connection    with, Illegal Activities.\n\nConsent to Collection of Information by Us - We are subject to AML/CTF Laws. You consent to us disclosing in connection with AML/CTF Laws any of your Personal Information (as defined in the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth)) we may have.\n\nFreezing or Blocking Transfer of Funds - In certain circumstances, we may be obliged to freeze or block an account where it is used in connection with Illegal Activities or suspected Illegal Activities. Freezing or blocking can arise as a result of the account monitoring that is required by AML/CTF Laws. If this occurs, we are not liable to you for any consequences or losses whatsoever and you agree to indemnify us if we are found liable to a third party in connection with the freezing or blocking of your account\n\nRight to Refuse to Provide Our Service – If you fail to provide to us upon request any information that we are required under the AML/CTF Laws to collect from\n\nThese terms and conditions are to be governed by any construed in accordance with the laws of New South Wales</string>
    <string name="register"><u><b>Register</b></u></string>
	<string name="userid"><u><b>User ID</b></u></string>
	<string name="password"><u><b>Password</b></u></string>
	<string name="app_id">385935261533331</string>
</resources>